{
    "subject": "resource/Volkhard_Eitner",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1914-01-02",
    "human_readable": "Volkhard Eitner was born on January 2, 1914.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8976572751998901,
            "question": "When was Volkhard Eitner born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8131487369537354,
            "question": "What month was Volkhard Eitner born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7477706670761108,
            "question": "What is Volkhard Eitner's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.745536208152771,
            "question": "On which day of the month was Volkhard Eitner born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6877602338790894,
            "question": "Were there any significant events happening in the world when Volkhard Eitner was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6032471060752869,
            "question": "What is Volkhard Eitner known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5930055379867554,
            "question": "How old is Volkhard Eitner now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5207745432853699,
            "question": "In what year did Volkhard Eitner enter the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4980902671813965,
            "question": "Could you tell me more about Volkhard Eitner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4486115872859955,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Volkhard Eitner's life and achievements?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Volkhard Eitner was born on January 2, 1914.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5643_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you tell me more about Volkhard Eitner?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5643_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Volkhard Eitner enter the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5643_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old is Volkhard Eitner now?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5643_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5643_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5643_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5643_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5643_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5643_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5643_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5643_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5643_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5643_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5643_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information and without prior knowledge, I can evaluate the triple.\n\nThe triple to be evaluated is:\n\"Volkhard Eitner was born on January 2, 1914.\"\n\nFrom the document with file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5643/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt, I can see that:\n\n\"Friday, January 2, 1914\"\n\nis mentioned as Volkhard Eitner's birthday. This information supports the triple.\n\nTherefore, my response is:\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Volkhard Eitner was born on January 2, 1914. This is explicitly stated in one of the files under the \"Birthday\" section."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}